Guide to the Yale School of Music Concert Programs
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
Yale School of Music concert programs
1888-1953
RU 461
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
3.25
(8 boxes)
The materials consist of programs from Yale School of Music student and faculty recitals and professional concerts held in Woolsey Hall and Sprague Memorial Hall.
Yale School of Music
General note
Forms part of Yale Record Group 28-E (YRG 28-E), Records of departments, offices, programs, and projects of the Yale School of Music.
Conditions Governing Access
The materials are open for research.
Arrangement
The materials are arranged chronologically.
Scope and Contents
The materials consist of programs from Yale School of Music student and faculty recitals and professional concerts held in Woolsey Hall and Sprague Memorial Hall.
Concert programs; Concerts; Conservatories of music; Programs; Yale School of Music; Yale University -- Faculty; Yale University -- Students
- Concert programs, 1888-1953; Accession 1954-A-002
  Scope and Contents
  Note: "Woolsey Hall Concert" folders include Woolsey Hall Concert Series programs, in addition to other programs. New Haven Symphony programs were removed because Manuscripts and Archives already has bound copies
  - Woolsey Hall, Sprague Hall, and Student and Faculty Concerts, 1888-1920 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - New Haven Oratorio Society, 1904, 1907 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Arthur Whiting Concerts [1924-1925 missing], 1920-1930 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Sprague Hall Concerts, 1920-1923 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Woolsey Hall Concerts, 1920-1923 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Miscellaneous, 1921-1944 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Sprague Hall Concerts, 1923-1925 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Woolsey Hall Concerts, 1923-1925 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Sprague Hall Concerts, 1925-1927 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Woolsey Ball Concerts, 1925-1927 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Sprague Hall Concerts, 1927-1929 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Woolsey Hall Concerts, 1927-1929 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Sprague Hall Coqcerts, 1929-1932 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Woolsey Hall Concerts, 1929-1932 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Sprague Hall Concerts, 1932-1935 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Woolsey Hall Concerts, 1932-1935 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Sprague Hall Concerts, 1935-1937 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Woolsey Hall Concerts, 1935-1937 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Sprague Hall Concerts, 1937-1938 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Woolsey Hall Concerts, 1937-1938 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Sprague Hall, and Student and Faculty Concerts, 1938-1939 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Woolsey Hall Concerts, 1938-1939 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Sprague Hall, and Student and Faculty Concerts, 1939-1940 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Woolsey Hall Concerts, 1939-1940 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Sprague Hall, and Student and Faculty Concerts, 1940-1941 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Woolsey Hall Concerts, 1940-1941 (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Sprague Hall, and Student and Faculty Concerts, 1941-1942 (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - Woolsey Hall Concerts, 1941-1942 (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - Sprague Hall, and Student and Faculty Concerts, 1942-1943 (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - Woolsey Hall Concerts, 1942-1943 (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - Sprague Wall and Student and Faculty Concerts, 1943-1944 (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - Woolsey Hall Concerts, 1943-1944 (Box 4, Folder 32)
  - Sprague Hall, and Student and Faculty Concerts, 1944-1945 (Box 4, Folder 33)
  - Woolsey Ball Concerts, etc., 1944-1945 (Box 5, Folder 34)
  - Sprague Hall, and student and Faculty Concerts, 1945-1946 (Box 5, Folder 35)
  - Woolsey Hall Concerts, 1945-1946 (Box 5, Folder 36)
  - Sprague Hall Concerts, 1946-1947 (Box 5, Folder 37)
  - Woolsey Hall Concerts, 1946-1947 (Box 5, Folder 38)
  - Sprague Hall Concerts, 1947-1948 (Box 5, Folder 39)
  - Woolsey Hall Concerts, 1947-1948 (Box 6, Folder 40)
  - Sprague Hall Concerts, 1948-1949 (Box 6, Folder 41)
  - Woolsey Hall Concerts, 1948-1949 (Box 6, Folder 42)
  - Chamber Music Concerts, etc., 1949-1950 (Box 6, Folder 43)
  - Sprague Hall Concerts, 1949-1950 (Box 6, Folder 44)
  - Woolsey Hall Concerts, 1949-1950 (Box 7, Folder 45)
  - Woolsey Hall Concert Series, 1949-1950 (Box 7, Folder 46)
  - Chamber Music Series, 1950-1951 (Box 7, Folder 47)
  - Student Recitals, 1950-1951 (Box 7, Folder 48)
  - Woolsey Hall Concerts, 1950-1951 (Box 7, Folder 49)
  - Chamber Music Series, 1951-1952 (Box 8, Folder 50)
  - Woolsey Hall Concerts, 1951-1952 (Box 8, Folder 51)
  - Sprague Hall Concerts, 1952-1953 (Box 8, Folder 52)
  - Woolsey Hall Concerts, 1952-1953 (Box 8, Folder 53)
- Woolsey Hall Organ Recital programs, Accession 2005-A-090
  - Organ recitals, 1907-1908 (Box 1)